Guide to the Grover Lewis Papers
The Wittliff Collections
- Published Work, 1955-2005
  - New West, "The Revenge of the Moldy Figs" - Corrected typescripts, October 24, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - New West, "The Revenge of the Moldy Figs" - Tear sheets, October 24, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - New West, "Bette and Aaron: One Sings and the Other Doesn't" - Editorial correspondence, March 13, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - New West, "Bette and Aaron: One Sings and the Other Doesn't" - General correspondence, March 13, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - New West, "Bette and Aaron: One Sings and the Other Doesn't" - Related materials, March 13, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - New West, "Bette and Aaron: One Sings and the Other Doesn't" - Corrected typescripts, March 13, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - New West, "Bette and Aaron: One Sings and the Other Doesn't" - Corrected proofs, March 13, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - New West, "Bette and Aaron: One Sings and the Other Doesn't" - Photostat, March 13, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - New West, "Bette and Aaron: One Sings and the Other Doesn't" - Tear sheets, March 13, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Editorial correspondence, March 27, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - General correspondence, March 27, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Wages of Sin correspondence, March 27, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Inter-office correspondence and Larry Flynt Publications, Inc. press releases, March 27, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Transcriptions of audio-taped interviews, March 27, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Transcriptions of audio-taped radio interviews with Lewis, a transcription of Tom Synder's interview with Lewis, and material related to these interviews, March 27, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Handwritten notes, March 27, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Wages of Sin material, March 27, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Related material, March 27, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Various newspapers and magazines published by Larry Flynt Publications, Inc., March 27, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Research material, March 27, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 3-4, Box 38, Folder 1-2)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Corrected typescripts, March 27, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Corrected page proofs, March 27, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Cover layout proof and cover tracing, March 27, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - New West, "The Debauchery, Redemption, Persecution and Attempted Assassination of Larry Flynt" - Tear sheets, March 27, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - New West, "American Fetish Art: Dry Bones" - Editorial correspondence, March 27, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - New West, "American Fetish Art: Dry Bones" - Corrected typescripts, March 27, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - New West, "American Fetish Art: Dry Bones" - Page proofs, March 27, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - New West, "American Fetish Art: Dry Bones" - Tear sheets, March 27, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - New West - Tear sheets, April 10, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - New West - Tear sheets, April 24, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - New West, "Buried Alive in Hype: My Years Among the Reality Vultures" - Editorial correspondence, May 22, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - New West, "Buried Alive in Hype: My Years Among the Reality Vultures" - General correspondence, May 22, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - New West, "Buried Alive in Hype: My Years Among the Reality Vultures" - Handwritten notes and newspaper clippings, May 22, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - New West, "Buried Alive in Hype: My Years Among the Reality Vultures" - Related material: Art/Gallery promo "Hype", May 22, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - New West, "Buried Alive in Hype: My Years Among the Reality Vultures" - Related material: Book/Publisher promo "Hype", May 22, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - New West, "Buried Alive in Hype: My Years Among the Reality Vultures" - Related material: Musician/Record label promo "Hype", May 22, 1978 (Box 39, Folder 6-7, Box 40, Box 41, Folder 1)
  - New West, "Buried Alive in Hype: My Years Among the Reality Vultures" - Related material: Movie promo "Hype", May 22, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 2-3)
  - New West, "Buried Alive in Hype: My Years Among the Reality Vultures" - Related material: Various other promo "Hype", May 22, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - New West, "Buried Alive in Hype: My Years Among the Reality Vultures" - Related material: "Hype" mentioned in article, May 22, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - New West, "Buried Alive in Hype: My Years Among the Reality Vultures" - Corrected typescripts, May 22, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - New West, "Buried Alive in Hype: My Years Among the Reality Vultures" - Page proofs, May 22, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - New West, "Buried Alive in Hype: My Years Among the Reality Vultures" - Tear sheets, May 22, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - New West, [Hank, Jr.] - Research, July 17, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - New West, [Hank, Jr.] - Handwritten notes, July 17, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - New West, [Hank, Jr.] - Transcription of interview with Hank Williams, Jr., April 21, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - New West, [Hank, Jr.] - Related material, July 17, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - New West, [Hank, Jr.] - Corrected typescripts, July 17, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - New West, "Sex and Manhood" - Editorial correspondence, December 4, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - New West, "Sex and Manhood" - General correspondence, December 4, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - New West, "Sex and Manhood" - Handwritten notes, December 4, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - New West, "Sex and Manhood" - Newspaper clippings, December 4, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - New West, "Sex and Manhood" - Related materia, December 4, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - New West, "Sex and Manhood" - Corrected typescripts and page proofs, December 4, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - New West, "Sex and Manhood" - Tear sheets, December 4, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - New West,"Farewell, My Lovely Gumshoe" - Corrected typescripts and page proofs, July 30, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - New West,"Farewell, My Lovely Gumshoe" - Tear sheets, July 30, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - New West, "Cook's Tour" - Correspondence, June 2, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - New West, "Cook's Tour" - Related material, June 2, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - New West, "Cook's Tour" - Research, June 2, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - New West, "Cook's Tour" - Handwritten and typed notes, June 2, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - New West, "Cook's Tour" - Transcription of audio-taped interview with Elisha Cook, June 2, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - New West, "Cook's Tour" - Page proofs, June 2, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - New West, "Cook's Tour" - Tear sheets, June 2, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - New West, review of John Kennedy Toole's A Confederacy of Dunces - Research, June 30, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - New West, review of John Kennedy Toole's A Confederacy of Dunces - Typescript, June 30, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - New West, review of John Kennedy Toole's A Confederacy of Dunces -, June 30, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - New West, "To Be or Not To Be Traven" - Tear sheets, October 6, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Oui, "Lash LaRue Whips It Out" - Editorial correspondence, January 1975 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Oui, "Lash LaRue Whips It Out" - Corrected typescripts, January 1975 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Oui, "Lash LaRue Whips It Out" - Published copy and tear sheets, January 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Pageant, "The Hardship of Being Barbra Streisand" - Research, November 1971 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Pageant, "The Hardship of Being Barbra Streisand" - Published copy, November 1971 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Playboy, "Is Randy Newman A Redneck Cole Porter—Or Just Strange?" - Typescript, November 1975 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Playboy, "Is Randy Newman A Redneck Cole Porter—Or Just Strange?" - Published copy and tear sheets, November 1975 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Playboy, "Who's the Bull Goose Loony Here" - Correspondence, December 1975 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Playboy, "Who's the Bull Goose Loony Here" - Related material, December 1975 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Playboy, "Who's the Bull Goose Loony Here" - Research, December 1975 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Playboy, "Who's the Bull Goose Loony Here" - Typed notes, December 1975 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Playboy, "Who's the Bull Goose Loony Here" - Typescript, December 1975 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Playboy, "Who's the Bull Goose Loony Here" - Tear sheets, December 1975 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Renaissance, "In Loco Parentis" (Volume 1, Number 4) - Published copy, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Rolling Stone, "Roaring Around with R. Redford" - Notes, April 15, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Rolling Stone, "Roaring Around with R. Redford" - Published copy, April 15, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Rolling Stone, "3 Dogs in big D: Bam, Bam, Bam"; "Splendor in the Short Grass" - Editorial correspondence, September 2, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Rolling Stone, "3 Dogs in big D: Bam, Bam, Bam"; "Splendor in the Short Grass" - Correspondence, September 2, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Rolling Stone, "3 Dogs in big D: Bam, Bam, Bam"; "Splendor in the Short Grass" - Related material, September 2, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Rolling Stone, "3 Dogs in big D: Bam, Bam, Bam"; "Splendor in the Short Grass" - "Splendor in the Short Grass: The Deer Park People in Texas" partial typescript, September 2, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Rolling Stone, "3 Dogs in big D: Bam, Bam, Bam"; "Splendor in the Short Grass" - Corrected typescript, September 2, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Rolling Stone, "3 Dogs in big D: Bam, Bam, Bam"; "Splendor in the Short Grass" - Published copy, September 2, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Rolling Stone, Promo for "I'll Be There in the Morning If I Live" - Related material, June 7, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Rolling Stone, Promo for "I'll Be There in the Morning If I Live" - Proof, June 7, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Rolling Stone, Promo for "I'll Be There in the Morning If I Live" - Color copy of published issue cover and selected pages, June 7, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Rolling Stone, "The Jeaning of Barbra Streisand" - Published copy, June 24, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Rolling Stone, "Jethro Tull" - Published copy, July 22, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Rolling Stone, "On the Set with Keach & Huston" - Published copy, September 30, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Rolling Stone, "Hitting the Note with the Allman Brothers Band" - Published copy, November 25, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Rolling Stone, "The Hollywood Film to End All"- Published copy, February 17, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Rolling Stone, "John Cassavetes Goes for the Edge" - Color copy of issue cover and selected pages, March 30, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Rolling Stone, "Soldier of the Heart"- Published copy, April 13, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Rolling Stone, "Hillbilly Heaven: Take the Mone and go Limp" - Published copy, April 27, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Rolling Stone, "Of Dope & Death: The Saga of Art Pepper" - Color copy of cover and selected pages, September 14, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Rolling Stone, "Sam Peckinpah in Mexico: Over-Learning with El Jefe" - Published copy, October 12, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Rolling Stone, "Boz Scagg's Life and, thus Far, Pretty Good Times" - Color copy of cover and selected pages, November 23, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Rolling Stone, "Lee Marvin's Great, Goddamned" - Published copy, December 21, 1972 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Rolling Stone, "A Conversation with the Nation's Oldest Citizen" - Color copy of cover and selected pages, February 1, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Rolling Stone, "The Last Celluloid Desperado" - Published copy, March 15, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Rolling Stone, promo for "I'll Be There In the Morning If I Live" - Color copy of cover and selected pages, May 10, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Rolling Stone, "The Redoubtable Mr. Newman" - Published copy and photostat, July 5, 1973 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - The Rolling Stone Reader - Correspondence, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - The Rolling Stone Reader - Promotional material, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - The Rolling Stone Reader - Published copy, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Splendor In The Short Grass - Typescript, 2005 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - St. Petersburg Times - General correspondence, 1984-1989 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Eugene Lourie's My Work in Films - Typescript, undated (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Bill Ganzel's Dust Bowl Descent - Typescript, September 9, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Bill Ganzel's Dust Bowl Descent - Published copy, September 9, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Stephen Crane's Stephen Crane: Prose and Poetry - Editorial correspondence, November 4, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Stephen Crane's Stephen Crane: Prose and Poetry - Typescript, November 4, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Stephen Crane's Stephen Crane: Prose and Poetry - Published copy, November 4, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of George Catlin's Drawings of North America - Editorial correspondence, November 13, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of George Catlin's Drawings of North America - Typescript, November 13, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Russell Martin and Marc Barasch's Writers of the Purple Sage: An Anthology of Recent Western Writing - Editorial correspondence, December 23, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Russell Martin and Marc Barasch's Writers of the Purple Sage: An Anthology of Recent Western Writing - Typescript, December 23, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Russell Martin and Marc Barasch's Writers of the Purple Sage: An Anthology of Recent Western Writing - Published copy, December 23, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - St. Petersburg Times, "The Legacy of Huckleberry Finn" - Correspondence, July 7, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - St. Petersburg Times, "The Legacy of Huckleberry Finn" - Related Material, July 7, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - St. Petersburg Times, "The Legacy of Huckleberry Finn" - Typescripts, July 7, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - St. Petersburg Times, "The Legacy of Huckleberry Finn" - Published copies and photocopies, July 7, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Barbara Leaming's Orson Welles: A Biography - Editorial correspondence, October 20, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Barbara Leaming's Orson Welles: A Biography - Research, October 20, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Barbara Leaming's Orson Welles: A Biography - Handwritten notes, October 20, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Barbara Leaming's Orson Welles: A Biography - Corrected typescripts, October 20, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Barbara Leaming's Orson Welles: A Biography - Published copy, October 20, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - St. Petersburg Times, "The Decline of Movies" - Correspondence, June 15, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - St. Petersburg Times, "The Decline of Movies" - Typescript, June 15, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - St. Petersburg Times, "The Decline of Movies" - Published copy, June 15, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of David Thomson's Warren Beatty and Desert Eyes: A Life and a Story - Typescripts, May 24, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of David Thomson's Warren Beatty and Desert Eyes: A Life and a Story - Published copy, May 24, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Dave Hickey's Prior Convictions: Stories from the Sixties - Editorial correspondence, July 16, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Dave Hickey's Prior Convictions: Stories from the Sixties - Research, July 16, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Dave Hickey's Prior Convictions: Stories from the Sixties - Handwritten and typed notes, July 16, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Dave Hickey's Prior Convictions: Stories from the Sixties - Typescript, July 16, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - St. Petersburg Times, review of Dave Hickey's Prior Convictions: Stories from the Sixties - Published copy, July 16, 1989 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Texas Monthly, "Farewell to Cracker Eden" - Typescripts, September 1992 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Texas Monthly, "Farewell to Cracker Eden" - Photocopy of published article, September 1992 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - The Village Voice - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - The Village Voice - Related material, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - The Village Voice, "Dripping Springs Reunion" - Corrected typescript, undated (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - The Village Voice, "Cowed in Cowtown" - Corrected typescript, undated (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - The Village Voice, "Baez at State" - Corrected typescript, undated (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - The Village Voice, "The End Crowd" - Corrected typescript, undated (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - The Village Voice, "Rolling Stone Speaks" - Corrected typescript, undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - The Village Voice, "Machine Show" - Corrected typescript, undated (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - The Village Voice, "Sutter's Gold" - Corrected typescript, undated (Box 47, Folder 35)
  - The Village Voice, "Michael Brody: Call the Keeper" - Corrected typescript, undated (Box 47, Folder 36)
  - The Village Voice, "Sick Transit Gloria"- Corrected typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - The Village Voice, "McGovern in Fat City"- Corrected typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - The Village Voice, "Park Station Bombing"- Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - The Village Voice, "Altamont Again"- Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - The Village Voice, "Altamont Review" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - The Village Voice, "Maysles Visit" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - The Village Voice, "Alcatraz Death" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - The Village Voice, "Altamont Murder Pictures" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - The Village Voice, "Santa Rita Film Approximately" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - The Village Voice, "People's Park Indictments" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - The Village Voice, "People's Pad" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - The Village Voice, "Family Dog Opening" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - The Village Voice, "Sand City Recall" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - The Village Voice, "Berkeley Calamities" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - The Village Voice, "Washbury '69: A Walk Along a Wet, Dead Street" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - The Village Voice, "Earthquake Party" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - The Village Voice, "Nixon Visits" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - The Village Voice, "Goon Bash" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - The Village Voice, "Monterey Festival" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - The Village Voice, "Altamont Aftermath" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - The Village Voice, "Altamont Murder Indictment" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - The Village Voice, "The Ides Cometh to S. F. State" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - The Village Voice, "So Long at the Faire" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - The Village Voice, "Stones Concert" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - The Village Voice, "Film Festival" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - The Village Voice, "Rock Fight" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - The Village Voice, "March in Berkeley" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - The Village Voice, "Newton Rally" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - The Village Voice, "The Band at Winterland" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - The Village Voice, "The Wild West" - Typescript, undated (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - The Washington Post, "Elisha Cook, Jr. Talks with Grover Lewis" - Transcript of interview with Elisha Cook, September 18, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - The Washington Post, "Elisha Cook, Jr. Talks with Grover Lewis" - Published copies, November 3, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  - The Washington Star - Published copy, March 20, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 33)
- Unpublished Work, 1958-1995
  This series is arranged alphabetically according to either title or subject of work. The bulk of this series is comprised of two large, unrealized projects: The Code of the West(a novel)and Goodbye If You Call That Gone (a memoir).
  Both of these projects reflect immensely important aspects of Lewis's life. The Code of the West reflects his intense love of the cinema—especially the bygone era of the Western. The material surrounding this project includes many handwritten and typed notes and an audio-taped interview with Diana Carey, a.k.a. "Baby Peggy," the famous child-actor of the early 1920's. Also notable here are handwritten notes concerning Lewis's work-in-progress by Gus Hasford, Lewis's friend and author of the famous Vietnam War novel, The Short-Timers.
  Goodbye If You Call That Gone remains unfinished due to Lewis's death from cancer in 1995. This was planned to be an expansive project in which he hoped to chronicle his own past — with both memory and fact — which centered on the tragic double-murder of both his parents in 1943. Included here are many photographs of Lewis's immediate and extended family, and extensive genealogical research. Other notable items are Lewis's book proposal accompanied by finished pages, both of which tell the fascinating story of his personal life and journalism career in his own words.
  Box 47 contains strictly unpublished material; boxes 48-62 comprise a sub-series, Unfinished Work, containing material relating to articles that remained unfinished.
  - "An Inventory of Woes" - Corrected typescript, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Golden Boot Awards - Editorial correspondence, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Golden Boot Awards - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Golden Boot Awards - Research, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Golden Boot Awards - Handwritten notes, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - "Hill and Link and Sodom and Gomorrah" - Typescript, circa 1969 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - "Inside Straight" - Correspondence, circa 1972 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - "Inside Straight" - Corrected typescript, circa 1972 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - "A Leaden Finger" - Corrected typescripts, undated (Box 49, Folder 9)